

10+ years of design experience and 3+ years of development experience, specializing in building scalable front-end products with great user experiences. I am looking for a hybrid UI/UX designer and developer position to support between design and development.

PORTFOLIO

Website jaykim-dev.netlify.app

CONTACT

Phone +1 (469) 386-6307

Email develop.jay8675@gmail.com

Address Dallas, Texas

SOCIAL

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/jay8675

Github github.com/jaehyung8675

SKILLS

Design User Experience (UX)

User Interface (UI)

Product Graphic Visual

Programming JavaScript

React Node.js Express.js HTML5 CSS

Sass / SCSS

Tools Adobe XD

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Figma Git Github

Visual Studio Code

EXPERIENCE

Visual Designer / Part-time

July 2017 - Present Richardson, Texas

Binnerri Presbyterian Church

- Create all visual designs for over 400+ members to engage them in worship and events.
- Revamp 2+ websites to make them more visually and experientially accessible to customers.
- Create presentations for speakers to support their sermons and easily interact with the audience.
- Complete projects on time and deliver them to clients according to the church's schedule and goals.

Sr. Web Designer / Developer

January 2020 - January 2023

OTA World LLC

Carrollton, Texas

- Led a design team to create and enhance all visual design, and maintained company websites.
- Responsible for maintaining content and style attributes of marketing and e-commerce pages.
- Knowledge of content management applications and creative marketing tools.
- Designed and developed product pages using JavaScript, HTML, and CSS, and used by over 100+ merchants (Costco, Amazon, Sam's Club, Home Depot, etc.) to market their sites.
- Managed projects using Agile to quickly deliver products to stakeholders, vendors, and customers.
- Created global CSS to enforce a consistent style across all Shopify e-commerce sites.

Graphic Designer

January 2014 - December 2014

Ravis's Ware House

Dallas, Texas

- Created print materials such as brochures and flyers to promote products that helped increase sales.
- Implemented lighting and design in a studio environment to produce product images.

Product Designer / Internship

January 2010 – January 2011

Pantech Wireless, Inc.

Seoul, South Korea

- Completed 2 major projects with all mobile design processes from concept to building mock-ups.
- Explored interactions and design ideas by creating storyboards, user flows, and prototypes.
- Collaborated with team members to implement new concept designs during the summer in Japan.

EDUCATION

University of North Texas	2020 – 2022
M.A. in Interaction Design	Denton, Texas

Southern Methodist UniversityB.F.A. in Art & Graphic Design Dallas, Texas

Brookhaven College2014 – 2017

A.A. in General Studies

Farmers Branch, Texas

Christian For The Nations Institute2012 - 2013Accredited Theological DegreeDallas, Texas

Hongik University2006 – 2010B.A. in Product DesignSejong, South Korea